<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><title>Wejure</title><link>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/</link><description>This site serves as documentation for the decentralized social network that operates on a peer-to-peer network written in Clojure.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 02:41:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><generator>clj-rss</generator><item><guid>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-02-17-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</guid><link>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-02-17-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</link><title>Using MUI as a Framework</title><description>In my previous blog, I have mentioned that I have switched from figwheel to shadow-cljs, and that I have also chosen to use Reagent for my web app.For the past two weeks, I have further chosen to use reagent-material-ui as the framework for my Reagent components. reagent-material-ui is a wrapper for MUI, which is a very popular framework for React components.</description><author>Oscar Jay LEW</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-02-03-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</guid><link>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-02-03-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</link><title>Switching to Shadow-Cljs</title><description>Following my last blog, I have been trying to find a ClojureScript library to allows me to interact with the Etherium blockchain.The library that is mentioned the most online is cljs-web3. In addition to this, I have decided to use the MetaMask extension as a gateway to connect to the Etherium blockchain. MetaMask is a cryptocurrency wallet and a gateway to blockchains. Without this extension, we would have to manually set up the user’s cryptocurrency account.</description><author>Oscar Jay LEW</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-01-20-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</guid><link>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-01-20-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</link><title>Using Reagent for my Web App</title><description>In the last blog, I mentioned that I was deciding between figwheel and shadow-cljs.After doing some research, I have chosen to use figwheel as my initial development tool for the web app, as it is written on the Clojure website that “figwheel-main has fewer moving parts than shadow-cljs and is therefore very simple to learn and work with”.</description><author>Oscar Jay LEW</author><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-01-06-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</guid><link>https://clojure-finance.github.io/wejure-website/Wejure-website/posts-output/2022-01-06-Blog-Post-Oscar-Jay-LEW/</link><title>A Decentralised Social Media</title><description>I have started my project on the 23rd of December and the goals for past two weeks were to conduct research on my topic which is decentralized social media and to learn about Clojure.As I have chosen to use blockchain to implement my project idea, I had to decide on which blockchain to use. After conducting research, I have decided to build my decentralized application (dApp) on top of Ethereum as it is one of the largest blockchains and it supports smart contracts. Although bitcoin also supports smart contracts, it was built with the intention of being an alternative to national currencies. Whereas for Ethereum, it was built for the purpose of facilitating programmatic contracts and applications, as according to Investopedia. As such, Ethereum has a stronger and more mature foundation on smart contracts.</description><author>Oscar Jay LEW</author><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>